A Guide to the Thomas N. Downing Papers, 1947-1977
Library of Virginia
- 87th Congress, 1961-1962. (Box 41)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, January-April 1961 (4 folders)
- 87th Congress, 1961-1962. (Box 42)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, May-December 1961 (8 folders)
    - Conditional Acceptances
    - Invitations Declined, January-April 1961 (4 folders)
- 87th Congress, 1961-1962. (Box 43)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Declined, May-December 1961 (8 folders)
    - Invitations Extended, 1961
    - Invitations Accepted, October-December 1962 [January-September omitted] (3 folders)
- 87th Congress, 1961-1962. (Box 44)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Declined, October-November 1962 [January-September, and December omitted] (2 folders)
    - Guest Book [1959-January 1963]
  - General Legislation.
    - Agriculture Legislation (2 folders)
    - Armed Forces
    - Atomic Energy
    - Autobmobile--Divorcing Manufacturers from Finance Business
    - Banking Legislation
    - Canners' Legislation
- 87th Congress, 1961-1962. (Box 45)
  - General Legislation.
    - Civil Defense Legislation
    - Civil Rights Legislation
    - Civil Service Legislation
    - Civil Service Retirement
    - Communications Legislation
    - Cruise Subsidy Bill
    - Depressed Areas
    - Disarmament Agency
    - District of Columbia
    - Educational TV
    - Equal Rights for Women
    - Federal Aid to Education (2 folders)
- 87th Congress, 1961-1962. (Box 46)
  - General Legislation.
    - Federal Aid to Education (1 folder)
    - Foreign Aid Legislation
    - Fuel Policy Legislation
    - General Legislation (2 folders)
- 87th Congress, 1961-1962. (Box 47)
  - General Legislation.
    - Highway Legislation
    - Housing Legislation
    - Imports and Exports Legislation
    - Department of the Interior
    - International Development
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce
    - Kennedy Legislative Program
    - Labor Legislation
    - Labor--Common Situs Picketing
- 87th Congress, 1961-1962. (Box 48)
  - General Legislation.
    - Medical Care for the Aged (3 folders)
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries.
    - Minimum Wage (3 folders)
- 87th Congress, 1961-1962. (Box 49)
  - General Legislation.
    - Minimum Wage--Seamen
    - Minimum Wage--Shellfish Exemption (3 folders)
    - Oceana School Property
- 87th Congress, 1961-1962. (Box 50)
  - General Legislation.
    - Oyster Bill
    - Oyster Disease Bill
    - Pay Raise Legislation
    - Pension Plan for Self-Employed Persons (H.R. 10)
    - Pesticides Legislation
    - Postal Legislation
    - Railroad Legislation (2 folders)
- 87th Congress, 1961-1962. (Box 51)
  - General Legislation.
    - Shellfish Legislation
    - Shoreline Preservation
    - Small Business Legislation
    - Social Security Legislation
    - Tariff Legislation
- 87th Congress, 1961-1962. (Box 52)
  - General Legislation.
    - Tax Equality Bill
    - Travel Service--Establishment of
    - Un-American Activities
    - Unemployment Compensation
    - United Nations Legislation
    - Veterans Legislation
    - Water Pollution Legislation
    - Wilderness Bill
  - Legislation Enacted.
    - Cherryman, Rexford R.--Relief (P.L. 87-588)
    - Oyster Planters (P.L. 87-832)
  - Legislation Not Enacted.
    - Tariff Reductions (H. Con. Res. 381)
    - Hampton National Cemetery (H.R. 9687)
    - Montgomery, Matsuyo Ishida (H.R. 1628)
- 87th Congress, 1961-1962. (Box 53)
  - News Releases and Publicity.
    - News Releases, 87th Congress
    - Your Congressman Reports
    - Radio/TV Reports
  - Political Files.
    - Democratic National Committee
    - Petitions, 1962 Primary
    - Political Promotion
    - Primary Election Returns, July 1961--Clippings
  - Speech Files.
    - Speech Material
- 87th Congress, 1961-1962. (Box 54)
  - Speech Files.
    - Speeches--General, 1961-1962
  - Veterans Affairs, 85th-87th Congresses, 1957-1962.
    - Veterans--General
    - A-G--General (7 folders)
    - Hudgins, Elizabeth Hodges
- 87th Congress, 1961-1962. (Box 55)
  - Veterans Affairs, 85th-87th Congresses, 1957-1962.
    - Hudson, Raymond B.
    - H-S [Q omitted]--General (12 folders)
    - Temporary Home for Soldiers and Sailors
    - T--General
- 87th Congress, 1961-1962. (Box 56)
  - Veterans Affairs, 85th-87th Congresses, 1957-1962.
    - V, W--General (2 folders)
  - Voting Record.
    - 1st and 2nd Sessions (2 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 56)
  - [Military] Academies.
    Military Academy files contain student academic records and are therefore restricted because of the Privacy Act. These records cannot be served.
    - Air Force Academy, 1963-1964 (2 folders)
    - Merchant Marine Academy, 1963-1964 (2 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 57)
  - [Military] Academies.
    - Military Academy, 1963-1964 (2 folders)
    - Naval Academy, 1963-1964 (2 folders)
    - Nominees and Nomination Information
    - Dropouts, 1963 Academy
  - General Files.
    - Accomack County
    - Accomplishments, 1963
    - Agriculture Department
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 58)
  - General Files.
    - Agriculture--Feedstock
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board
    - American Legion
    - Appointments of Mr. Downing--General
    - Area Redevelopment Program--Eastern Shore
    - Auditorium for Peninsula
    - A--General
    - Bar Association
    - Beach Erosion
    - Biographies
    - Birth Certificates
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 59)
  - General Files.
    - Board of Visitors--Merchant Marine Academy
    - Boatmen
    - B--General (2 folders)
    - Cape Charles
    - Cape Henry
    - Cedar Island
    - Chamber of Commerce
    - Chesapeake Bay Bridge Tunnel
    - Chincoteague
    - Civil Service Commission
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 60)
  - General Files.
    - Colleges and College Admission
    - Commemorative Stamps
    - Commerce Department
    - Congratulations (2 folders)
    - Congressional Directory
    - Congressional Record
    - Alan B. Shepard Convention Center
    - Cuban Situation
    - C--General (1 folder)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 61)
  - General Files.
    - C--General (1 folder)
    - Delmarva Soybean Processors--ARA Loan
    - Democratic National Convention--Passes
    - Denbigh
    - District Office--1st District
    - Duties of a Congressman
    - D--General
    - Eastern Shore
    - Editorials Considered for Publication
    - Essex County
    - E--General
    - Federal Communications Commission [FCC] (1 folder)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 62)
  - General Files.
    - Federal Communications Commission [FCC] (1 folder)
    - Federal Flood Control
    - Flags
    - Football Tickets--Army-Navy Game
    - F--General
    - Gallery Passes
    - General Services Administration [GSA]
    - Gloucester County
    - G--General
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 63)
  - General Files.
    - Hampton
    - Hampton Institute
    - Hampton Roads Maritime Association
    - Harrison Lake National Fish Hatchery
    - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare [HEW]
    - Highway Department
    - Housing
    - H--General (2 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 64)
  - General Files.
    - Immigration and Naturalization--Dr. Naim Balta
    - Interstate Commerce Commission [ICC]
    - Imports and Exports (2 folders)
    - Interior Department
    - Internal Revenue Service [IRS]
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 65)
  - General Files.
    - I--General
    - James City County
    - Jamestown
    - Justice Department
    - J--General
    - Kennedy, John F.
    - K--General
    - Labor Department
    - Land Acquisitions
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 66)
  - General Files.
    - Libraries--1st District
    - Library of Congress
    - L--General
    - Maritime Administration [MARAD]
    - Mathews County
    - Maury, Matthew Fontaine
    - M--General (1 folder)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 67)
  - General Files.
    - M--General (2 folders)
    - NASA (2 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 68)
  - General Files.
    - NASA (1 folder)
    - Other Committee Assignments
    - O--General
    - Page School
    - Parramore Island
    - Pardons and Paroles
    - Passports
    - Peninsula Chamber of Commerce
    - Peninsula Shipbuilders Association
    - Photographs--Requests for
    - Pollution
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 70)
  - General Files.
    - Post Office Department
    - Presidents
    - Princess Anne
    - Providence Forge
    - P--General
    - Questionnaires
    - Reforestation Cost Deductions
    - Reserve Officers Association
    - R--General
    - Saluda
    - Scholarships
    - Shipbuilders Council of America
    - Small Business Administration [SBA]
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 71)
  - General Files.
    - Soil Conservation District
    - State Department (2 folders)
    - Sudeten German Day--Dr. Becher
    - Supreme Court
    - Surplus Property
    - S--General (2 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 72)
  - General Files.
    - S--General (1 folder)
    - Tappahannock
    - Test Ban Treaty
    - Travel Development Association of Eastern Virginia
    - Treasury Department
    - TRECOM [U.S. Army Transportation Research Command]
    - T--General
    - United Nations
    - University of Virginia
    - Urban Renewal
    - Commonwealth of Virginia
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 73)
  - General Files.
    - Virginia Beach
    - Virginia Beach Travel Association
    - Virginia Military Institute
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute
    - U, V--General (2 folders)
    - White House
    - Colonial Williamsburg, Inc.
    - W--General (2 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 74)
  - General Files.
    - W--General [including Capt. Robert B. Wood--Nuclear Power in Marine Transportation Systems] (1 folder)
    - Yorktown
    - X-Z--General
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, January-July 1963 (7 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 75)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, August-December 1963 (5 folders)
    - Invitations Regretted, January-November 1963 (11 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 76)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Regretted, December 1963
    - Day-at-a-Glance Daybook, 1963
    - Invitations Accepted, January-December 1964 (12 folders)
    - Invitations Regretted, January 1964
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 77)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Regretted, February-December 1964 (11 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 78)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Extended--Strawberry Banks, 11 September 1964
    - Day-at-a-Glance Daybook, 1964
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - Agriculture (3 folders)
    - Agriculture--Wheat Legislation
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 79)
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - Appropriations Committees (2 folders)
    - Armed Services Committee (2 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 80)
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - Banking and Currency Committee
    - Banking and Currency--Backdoor Spending
    - District of Columbia Committee
    - District of Columbia--Firearms--Judiciary
    - Dual Office and Compensation Act
    - Education and Labor Committee (2 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 81)
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - Education and Labor Committee (2 folders)
    - Foreign Affairs Committee
    - Government Operations
    - House Administration Committee
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 82)
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - Immigration and Naturalization (2 folders)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs (2 folders)
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce [IFC] (1 folder)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 83)
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee--H.R. 4700 (4 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 84)
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee--H.R. 4700 (1 folder)
    - Judiciary Committee--General (2 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 85)
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - Judiciary Committee--General (1 folder)
    - Judiciary Committee--General--January 1964
    - Judiciary Committee--Becker Amendment (3 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 86)
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - Judiciary Committee--Civil Rights--January 1964
    - Judiciary Committee--Immigration
    - Judiciary Committee--Prayers (3 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 87)
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries
    - Patronage Committee
    - Pay Bill
    - Post Office and Civil Service (2 folders)
    - Public Works
    - Rules Committee
    - Science and Astronautics (2 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 88)
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - Senate Foreign Relations Committee
    - Small Business Administration [SBA]
    - Tax Cut Legislation (3 folders)
    - Un-American Activities
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 89)
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - Veterans Affairs Committee
    - War Department:
      - Air Force
      - Army
      - A, B--General (2 folders)
      - Civil Defense
      - Coast Guard
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 90)
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - War Department:
      - C--General
      - Defense Department
      - Dillon Report
      - D, E--General (2 folders)
      - Fort Eustis
      - Fort Monroe
      - Fort Story
      - F--General
      - General--Armed Forces
      - Gerber, [CWO Charles]
      - G--General
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 91)
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - War Department:
      - H-K [I omitted]--General (3 folders)
      - Langley Air Force Base
      - Little Creek Amphibious Base
      - L, Mc--General (2 folders)
      - Military Bands
      - M--General
      - Naval Air Station Oceana
      - Naval Public Works Center
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 92)
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - War Department:
      - Naval Weapons Center
      - Navy
      - Norfolk Air Reserve Center
      - Norfolk Naval Shipyard
      - N-Q--General (4 folders)
      - Reserves
      - R--General
      - Selective Service
      - Sonic Booms
      - S--General
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 93)
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - War Department:
      - T-V--General (3 folders)
      - Wage Board
      - West Gate Access Road
      - W-Z--General (2 folders)
    - Ways and Means Committee (3 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 94)
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - Bills, 88th Congress
  - Legislation Enacted.
    - Over-payment Legislation (P.L. 88-151)
    - Shorter, Herbert B., Sr. (P.L. 88-83)
    - Wood, John F.--Relief (P.L. 88-251)
  - Legislation Not Enacted, 1st Session.
    - Compulsory Arbitration (2 folders)
    - Congressional Medal of Honor [GEN Lewis B. Puller]
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 95)
  - Legislation Not Enacted, 1st Session.
    - Ethics Committee (H. Res. 336)
    - Green, Col. Warren J.--Relief (H.R. 13145)
    - Judgeship--Eastern District of Virginia (3 folders)
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries.
    - Mosquito Control Bill (3 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 96)
  - Legislation Not Enacted, 1st Session.
    - Renegotiation Act Clarification (H.R. 9395)
    - Vessel Manning Requirements
  - Legislation Not Enacted, 2nd Session.
    - Holland Society of America--to Incorporate (H.R. 11559)
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries.
  - Marine Foodstuffs--Information Regarding, various dates.
    - The American Shellfisheries Act of 1963 (2 folders).
      Note: See also Boxes 49, 50, 51.
    - Chesapeake Seafood
    - Disaster Loan (H.R. 946)
    - Marshlands
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 97)
  - Master Files [1964 only].
    - A-J (10 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 98)
  - Master Files [1964 only].
    - K-T (11 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 99)
  - Master Files [1964 only].
    - U-Z (4 folders)
  - Political Files.
    - Petitions, 1964 Primary
    - Reelection, 1964
  - Veterans Affairs, 1961-1964.
    - Arlington National Cemetery, Virginia
    - A-C--General (3 folders)
    - Delinquent Accounts
    - D-F--General (3 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 100)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1961-1964.
    - General Veterans File
    - G-J--General (4 folders)
    - Kecoughtan Veterans Center
    - K-S--General (10 folders)
- 88th Congress, 1963-1964. (Box 101)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1961-1964.
    - T, W [U, V, X, Y, Z omitted]--General (2 folders)
  - Voting Record.
    - 1st and 2nd Sessions (2 folders)
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 101)
  - [Military] Academies.
    Military Academy files contain student academic information; they are therefore restricted due to Privacy Act considerations and may not be served.
    - U.S. Air Force Academy, 1965-1966 (2 folders)
    - Merchant Marine Academy, 1965-1966 (3 folders)
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 102)
  - [Military] Academies.
    - Military Academy, 1965-1966 (2 folders)
    - Naval Academy, 1965-1966 (2 folders)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Agriculture--Legislation
    - Agriculture--Federal Bank for REA
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 103)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Agriculture--Food for Freedom--Downing Amendment
    - Agriculture--School Lunch Program
    - Agriculture--Yearbook, 1966
    - Appropriations Committee
    - Armed Services Committee--Legislation
    - Armed Services Committee--Closing of Commissary Stores
    - Banking and Currency
    - District of Columbia Committee
    - Education and Labor--Legislation
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 104)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Education and Labor--Aid to Education--Form Letter
    - Education and Labor--Aid to Education--Downing's Vote
    - Education and Labor--Minimum Wage--Downing's Amendment
    - Education and Labor--Situs Picketing (H.R. 10027)
    - National Commission on Food Marketing--Background Material
    - Foreign Affairs Committee
    - Interior and Insular Affairs--Legislation
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce
    - Joint Committee on Atomic Energy
    - Judiciary Committee--Legislation
    - Judiciary Committee--Immigration--Quota System
    - Judiciary Committee--Voting Rights
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries.
    - Joint Committee on the Organization of the Congress
    - Post Office and Civil Service Committee--Legislation
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 105)
  - General Legislation [and Committees].
    - Post Office and Civil Service--National Association of Retired Civil Employees [NARCE]--1966 legislation
    - Public Works Committee--General
    - Public Works Committee--Beautification Bill
    - Rules Committee
    - Science and Astronautics Committee (2 folders)
    - Select Committee on Small Business
    - Senate Commerce Committee
    - V[eterans] A[ffairs] Legislation
    - Ways and Means--Legislation
    - Ways and Means--Medicare
  - General Files [and General Legislation].
    - Accomack County
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 106)
  - General Files [and General Legislation].
    - Accomplishments, 1965-1966
    - Agriculture Department
    - Aid for International Development [AID]
    - Air Force
    - American Legion
    - Appointments, 1966
    - Area Redevelopment [ARA]
    - Armed Forces--General
    - Army
    - Assateague Island--General
    - Atlantic Express Line
    - A--General
    - Bellamy Award--Margarette S. Miller
    - Big Island Emergency Relief Committee
    - Brout, Al--Community Cultural Center
    - B--General
    - Camp Perry
    - National Canners Association Convention, 25 January 1966
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 107)
  - General Files [and General Legislation].
    - Cape Charles
    - Cedar Island and Parramore Island Seashore Park
    - Chambers of Commerce
    - Charles City County
    - Cheatham Annex--Blood Storage
    - Cheatham Annex--W&N
    - Chincoteague
    - Coast Guard
    - Coast Guard--Closing of Stations
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 108)
  - General Files [and General Legislation].
    - College Admissions
    - Colonial National Historical Park
    - Commemorative Stamps
    - Commerce Department
    - Committee Assignments
    - Community Concert Association
    - Congratulations--General
    - Crown National Bank
    - Customs--General (2 folders)
    - C--General
    - Delmarva
    - Democratic Party in Virginia
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 109)
  - General Files [and General Legislation].
    - Department of Defense
    - Disaster Relief
    - District Office
    - D--General
    - Leif Erickson Day, 1965-1966
    - Extension of Remarks (2 folders)
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 110)
  - General Files [and General Legislation].
    - Federal Communications Commission [FCC]
    - Federal Housing Administration [FHA]
    - Federal Power Commission [FPC]
    - Federal Trade Commission [FTC]
    - Flags
    - Fort Eustis
    - Fort Monroe
    - Football Tickets
    - F--General
    - Gallery Passes
    - General Legislation
    - General Services Administration [GSA]
    - G--General
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 111)
  - General Files [and General Legislation].
    - Hampton
    - Hampton Institute
    - Hampton Roads Maritime Association
    - Hampton Roads Sanitation District Commission
    - Health, Education and Welfare [HEW]
    - Highways--General
    - Hill-Burton Grant--Public Health Service [PHS]
    - Holly Sugar Corporation
    - Housing
    - H--General
    - Immigration
    - Imports and Exports
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 112)
  - General Files [and General Legislation].
    - Inauguration, 1965 (2 folders)
    - Department of the Interior
    - Interior--Duck Hunting
    - Internal Revenue Service [IRS]
    - Interstate Commerce Commission [ICC]
    - I--General
    - Jack Clamp
    - James, Eldon
    - James City
    - Jokes
    - Justice Department
    - J, K--General (2 folders)
    - Department of Labor
    - Langley Air Force Base
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 113)
  - General Files [and General Legislation].
    - Library of Congress
    - L--General
    - Maritime Administration [MARAD]
    - Marshall, Clarence
    - M--General
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration [NASA]
    - NASA--Wallops Island
    - National Park Service
    - Navy
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 114)
  - General Files [and General Legislation].
    - Naval Air Station Oceana
    - Naval Shipyards
    - Naval Weapons Station
    - Newport News, City of
    - Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Co.
    - News Releases, 89th Congress
    - Norfolk Chamber of Commerce
    - Norfolk, City of
    - Norfolk Naval Shipyard
    - Northampton County
    - N--General
    - Office of Economic Opportunity
    - Office Expenses
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 115)
  - General Files [and General Legislation].
    - Office Supplies and Services
    - Old Dominion College
    - Onancock
    - O--General
    - Parramore Island
    - Patrick Henry Airport
    - Patronage
    - Peace Corps
    - Peninsula Arena/Auditorium Authority
    - Pharmacists
    - Phoebus
    - Port of Hampton Roads
    - Posst Office Department
    - Photographs (2 folders)
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 116)
  - General Files [and General Legislation].
    - Photographs (3 folders)
    - Photographs, 1953-1956 [filed with 89th Congress photographs]
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 117)
  - General Files [and General Legislation].
    - P-R--General (3 folders)
    - Selective Service
    - Small Business Administration [SBA]
    - Social Security
    - State Department
    - Surplus Property
    - S--General
    - Tangier
    - Tangier--Doctor for
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 118)
  - General Files [and General Legislation].
    - T--General
    - Veterans Administration [VA]
    - Virginia Associated Research Center
    - Virginia Beach, City of
    - Commonwealth of Virginia